Register to the Papers of Kurt Weill and Lotte Lenya
Yale University Music Library
- Programs, 1931-1981; Series V; 1.7' (4 boxes)
  - Works by Others and Miscellaneous Items, V.B
    - Works by others and miscellaneous programs, 1942-1981; 41 items. (Box 56, Folder 40-41)
    - Broadsides and exhibit catalogs, 1936-1979; 27 items. (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Press releases and publisher announcements, 1942-1981; 16 items. (Box 56, Folder 43-45)
    - Published calendars of events, 1936-1981; 15 items. (Box 56, Folder 46)
- Photographs, 1900-1981; Series VI; 4.6' (11 boxes)
  Subseries A-K are arranged either chronologically or alphabetically by name or title of work. Cross-references have been made for photographs which contain two or more identified individuals.
  - Weill, VI.A
    - Weill alone, 1919-1946; 27 items. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Lenya, VI.B
    - Lenya alone, 1900-1923; 19 items. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Lenya alone, 1928-1929; 16 items. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Lenya alone, 1931-1935; 12 items. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Lenya alone, 1931; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Lenya alone, 1937-1942; 12 items. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Lenya alone, 1944-1955; 23 items. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Lenya alone, 1957-1958; 19 items. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Lenya alone, 1960-1965; 21 items. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Lenya alone, 1966-1969; 72 items. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Lenya alone, 1971-1979; 86 items. (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Lenya alone, 1979; 4 items. (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Lenya alone, 1980-1981; 20 items. (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Lenya alone, n.d.; 71 items. (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Lenya alone, n.d.; 66 items. (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Lenya alone, n.d.; 17 items. (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Lenya alone, n.d.; 38 items. (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Lenya alone, n.d.; 27 items. (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Lenya alone, n.d.; 7 items. (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Lenya alone, n.d.; 2 items. (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Lenya alone - Contact sheets, n.d.; 29 items. (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Weill and Lenya, VI.C
    - Weill and Lenya together, 1935-1945; 15 items. (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Photograph album containing 49 photographs of Kurt Weill and Lenya as well as Margarethe Kaiser and others., 1916-[1920s]; 1 item. (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Weill and Others, VI.D
    - Weill with Anderson, Busoni, Ira Gershwin, Edwin Justus Meyer, Weisgal, Werfel, and others., 1920-1945; 10 items. (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Lenya with Others, VI.E
    - Photographs, 1951-1968; 21 items. (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Andriola, Alfred
      - Aufricht, Ernst Josef
        See also: K. Lenya Recordings. Dreigroschenoper (1958).
      - Beatty, Warren
      - Becker, Werner
      - Braun, ? [Herr Direktor]
        See: Thielemann, Gudrun.
      - Breuer, Bessie
      - Brückner-Rüggeberg, Wilhelm
      - Buckiwtz, Harry
    - Photographs, 1966-1975; 14 items. (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Caniff, Milton
      - Carl, Victor
      - Case, Bertha
      - Cavett, Dick
    - Photographs, 1962-1971; 48 items. (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Dall, Irene
        See: Ebert, Carl.
      - Daniels, Mary
      - Davis, George
        See also: Fujita; Weisenborn.
      - Detwiler, Russell
      - Drew, David
    - Photographs, [1939]-1962; 7 items. (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - Ebert, Carl
      - Eve, Maisie [of Le Ruban Bleu]
    - Photographs, 1965-1966; 23 items. (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Fleming, Janet
      - Fujita, S. Neil, Aiko, and family
        See also: Drew, David.
    - Photographs, 1955-1975; 35 items. (Box 59, Folder 28)
      - Grey, Joel
        See also: Merrill, Scott.
      - Harris, Margo
      - Hassforth, "Mama" and "Papa"
      - Heinsheimer, Hans
      - Jacoby, ? [of Le Ruban Bleu]
        See: Eve, Maisie.
      - "Mr. John"
    - Photographs, 1923-1979; 44 items. (Box 59, Folder 29)
      - Kaiser, Margarethe (Mrs. Georg) and family
      - Keller, Grete
      - Krebs, Anna
      - Kreisler, Marshall
      - Krutz, Dr. and Mrs.
      - Lerner, Alan Jay
      - Lichthorn, Suzanne
      - Lindsay, John
    - Photographs, 1958-1980; 10 items. (Box 59, Folder 30)
      - Martini, Paul
      - Menotti, Gian Carlo
      - Merrill, Scott
      - Mitchell, Ted
      - Murphy, Turk
      - Neher, Caspar
      - Nilsson, Birgit
      - Pauli, [Hansjorg?] [German consul in New York]
      - Rieker, Charles
    - Photographs, 1972-1981; 39 items. (Box 59, Folder 31)
      - Schmelling, Max
      - Schuetz, Klaus
      - Schuller, Gunther
      - Stern, Guy
      - Stone, Ruth and Walter
      - Stratas, Teresa
      - Symonette, Lys
        See also: Harris, Margo.
      - Symonette, Victor
    - Photographs, 1956; 11 items. (Box 59, Folder 32)
      - Thielemann, Gudrun
      - Toch, Ernst
      - Ullmann, Liv
        See: Nilsson, Birgit.
    - Photographs, 1955-1976; 21 items. (Box 59, Folder 33)
      - Unseld, Dr.
      - Varnay, Astrid
      - Wagner, Gottfried
      - Wecker, Dr.
      - Weill, Rita
        See: Lerner, Alan Jay.
      - Weisenborn, Gunther
        See also: K. Lenya Recordings.
      - Wilder, Jo
        See: Grey, Joel.
    - Unidentified individuals, 1928-1980; 54 items. (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified individuals, 42 items. (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Lenya with larger groups of people, 1967-[1979]; 23 items. (Box 59, Folder 36)
      With Detwiler, Ted Mitchell, "Pete," and others.
      With Guy Stern, Margarethe Kaiser, and others.
      With Detwiler, Janet Fleming, Margo Harris, and unidentified woman.
      White House luncheon at the invitation of President Johnson for the President of Iceland.
      With casts from Cabaret and other Broadway shows.
      With unidentified individuals at Holland Festival?.
      With Charles Rieker and others.
      United Nations dinner with Ambassador Fack of The Netherlands, Mrs. Dorothy Huston, Mrs. Nadya Post, Hank Kaufman, and others.
  - Weill's Staged Works, VI.F
    - Aufstieg und Fall der Stadt Mahagonny, 1974; 2 items. (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Die Bürgschaft, 1932-1957; 10 items. (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, 1928-1930; 11 items. (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, 1928-1930; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, 1954; 120 items. (Box 60, Folder 40-42)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper - Contact sheets., 1954; 83 items. (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, 1957; 1 item. (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, 1965 Jun. 30; 7 items. (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, 1973-1974; 11 items. (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, n.d.; 79 items. (Box 61, Folder 46)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, n.d.; 12 items. (Box 61, Folder 47)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Eternal Road, 1937; 6 items. (Box 61, Folder 48)
    - Firebrand of Florence, 1945; 9 items. (Box 61, Folder 49)
    - Happy End, 1929; 3 items. (Box 61, Folder 50)
    - Huckleberry Finn, ca. 1964 Dec. 19; 3 items. (Box 61, Folder 51)
    - Der Jasager, 1933-1955; 4 items. (Box 61, Folder 52)
    - Johnny Johnson, 1936; 3 items. (Box 61, Folder 53)
    - Kingdom for a Cow, 1935; 1 item. (Box 61, Folder 54)
    - Knickerbocker Holiday, 1938; 3 items. (Box 61, Folder 55)
    - Lady in the Dark, 1941-1972; 14 items. (Box 61, Folder 56)
    - Lost in the Stars, 1949-1962; 33 items. (Box 61, Folder 57)
    - Love Life, 1947; 3 items. (Box 61, Folder 58)
    - Magna Carta, 1976; 6 items. (Box 61, Folder 59)
    - Mahagonny [Songspiel], 1927-1931; 7 items. (Box 61, Folder 60)
    - One Touch of Venus, 1944; 5 items. (Box 61, Folder 61)
    - Petroleuminseln, 1929; 3 items. (Box 61, Folder 62)
    - Royal Palace, 1925; 3 items. (Box 61, Folder 63)
    - Die sieben Todsünden, 1933; 3 items. (Box 61, Folder 64)
    - Die sieben Todsünden, 1958 Dec.; 27 items. (Box 61, Folder 65)
    - Die sieben Todsünden, 1960-1980; 24 items. (Box 61, Folder 66)
    - Der Silbersee, 1971; 9 items. (Box 61, Folder 67)
    - Street Scene, 1947-1955; 22 items. (Box 61, Folder 68)
    - Der Zar lässt sich photographieren, 1927; 2 items. (Box 61, Folder 69)
  - Lenya Performances of Non-Weill Works, VI.G
    - The Appointment, 1966; 5 items. (Box 62, Folder 70)
      With Omar Shariff.
    - Brecht on Brecht, 1963; 25 items. (Box 62, Folder 71)
    - Cabaret, 1966-1969; 32 items. (Box 62, Folder 72)
      With Bert Convy, Jack Gilford, and Jill Hayworth.
    - Camino Real, 1966; 11 items. (Box 62, Folder 73)
      Play by Tennessee Williams. With Martin Sheen.
    - Candle in the Wind, 1941-1942; 4 items. (Box 62, Folder 74)
      Play by Maxwell Anderson. Directed by Alfred Lunt. With Helen Hayes.
    - Danton's Death, 1929; 2 items. (Box 62, Folder 75)
      Play by Büchner.
    - From Berlin to Broadway, 1972; 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 76)
    - From Russia with Love, 1963; 40 items. (Box 62, Folder 77)
      Film. Book by Ian Fleming. With Sean Connery.
    - Frühlings Erwachen, 1929; 4 items. (Box 62, Folder 78)
      Play by Wedekind. With Peter Lorre.
    - German television program, 1956 Oct. 7; 6 items. (Box 62, Folder 79)
    - Harte Bandagen, 1929; 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 80)
      Play by Ferdinand Rayber.
    - Jud Süss, 1929; 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 81)
      Play by Paul Kornfeld.
    - Lied von Hoboken, 1929-1932; 10 items. (Box 62, Folder 82)
    - Lotte Lenya singt Kurt Weill, 1968; 7 items. (Box 62, Folder 83)
      For German television.
    - Mutter Courage, 1960-1973; 41 items. (Box 62, Folder 84-86)
      Play by Brecht.
    - Oedipus, 1929; 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 87)
      Play by Sophocles.
    - "Omnibus", 1978-1979; 2 items. (Box 62, Folder 88)
      For BBC-TV.
    - Pioniere in Ingolstadt, 1929; 6 items. (Box 62, Folder 89)
      Play by Marieluise Fleisser.
    - Die Quadratur des Kreises, 1929-1930; 2 items. (Box 62, Folder 90)
      Play by Igor Katayev.
    - Roman Spring of Mrs. Stone, 1961; 21 items. (Box 62, Folder 91)
      Film. By Tennessee Williams, directed by Jose Quintero. With Vivien Leigh, Warren Beatty, and Jill St. John.
    - Schuyler Chapin public television interview, 1978-1979; 25 items. (Box 62, Folder 92)
    - Semi-Tough, 1976; 7 items. (Box 62, Folder 93)
      Film with Burt Reynolds.
    - "Today Show", 1975 May; 15 items. (Box 62, Folder 94)
      With Gene Shalit.
    - Wie Werde Ich Reich und Glücklich, 1933; 3 items. (Box 62, Folder 95)
    - World of Kurt Weill, 1964-1966; 26 items. (Box 62, Folder 96)
      Television.
    - Zurich Ballet, ca. 1916; 16 items. (Box 62, Folder 97)
  - Lenya Concert Performances, VI.H
    - Brandeis, Lewisohn Stadium, Carnegie Hall, 1952-1960; 20 items. (Box 63, Folder 98)
    - Munich, 1960; 37 items. (Box 63, Folder 99)
    - University of Cincinnati, Greenwich Philharmonia, 1969-1978; 18 items. (Box 63, Folder 100)
  - New York Public Library Exhibit, VI.I
    - NYPL exhibit, 1975; 28 items. (Box 63, Folder 101)
  - Professional Postcards of Lenya, VI.J
    - Professional postcards of Lenya, n.d.; 43 items. (Box 63, Folder 102)
  - Lenya Recordings, VI.K
    - Johnny Johnson, "Lotte Lenya singt Kurt Weill", 1954-1957; 9 items. (Box 63, Folder 103)
    - Aufstieg und Fall der Stadt Mahagonny, 1956; 38 items. (Box 63, Folder 104)
    - "Mack the Knife", 1956; 2 items. (Box 63, Folder 105)
      With Turk Murphy.
    - "September Song" album, 1957; 16 items. (Box 63, Folder 106)
    - Die Dreigroschenoper, 1958; 53 items. (Box 63, Folder 107-8)
      See also: E. Lenya and Others. Aufricht, Ernst Josef.
    - "Mack the Knife", 1959; 12 items. (Box 63, Folder 109)
      With Louis Armstrong.
    - Recording shots in Hamburg, n.d.; 247 items. (Box 63, Folder 110-11)
  - Weill Family, VI.L
    - Weill family, 1929-1942; 8 items. (Box 64, Folder 112)
  - Lenya Family, VI.M
    - Lenya family, 1917-1976; 51 items. (Box 64, Folder 113)
  - Others, VI.N
    - Individuals, VI.N.1
      - Photographs, 1935-1979; 13 items. (Box 64, Folder 114)
        - Anderson, Hesper
        - Anderson, Maxwell
        - Andriola, Alfred
        - Aufricht, Margot
        - Bering, Joan
          See: Young, Louise.
        - Brecht, Bertolt
        - Breuer, Bessie
        - Cahill, Frank
        - Carl, Victor
        - Case, Bertha
        - Charreau, Dolly
      - Photographs, 1966; 18 items. (Box 64, Folder 115)
        - Daniels, Mary
        - Davis, George
      - Detwiler, Russell, 1941-1968; 71 items. (Box 64, Folder 116)
      - Detwiler, Russell and friends, 1944-1968; 126 items. (Box 64, Folder 117)
      - Photographs, 1934-1976; 22 items. (Box 64, Folder 118)
        - Fujita, S. Neil, Aiko, and family
        - Gordon, Ruth
        - Grey, Joel and family
        - Guerneri, Victor
        - Hammerschlag, Dr.
        - Harchen, Christian
        - Harris, Margo
        - Heaven, Peter Stone
        - Huston, Nan
        - Huston, Walter
        - "Mr. John"
        - Jones, Billy
      - Photographs, 1923-1978; 37 items. (Box 64, Folder 119)
        - Kaiser, Georg
        - Kaiser, Margarethe
        - Koczian, Johanna V.
        - Krebs, Anna
        - Kreuzer, Anton
      - Photographs, 1916-1980; 26 items. (Box 64, Folder 120)
        - Lynes, George Platt
        - McGuire, Gigi
        - McPherson, Kenneth
        - Mario, Paul
        - Marx, Manny
        - Mendelssohn, Eleonora von
        - Meredith, Burgess
        - Merrill, Scott
        - Milhaud, Darius
        - Milhaud, Madeleine
        - Mitchell, Ted
        - Neher, Erika [?]
        - Pasetti, Mario
        - "Pete" [caretaker of Brook House]
        - Quintero, Jose
      - Photographs, 1928-1978; 25 items. (Box 64, Folder 121)
        - Ragalyi, Gerda
        - Reininger, Lotte
        - Schellow, Erich
        - Shariff, Omar
        - Siemanowski, Richard
        - Stone, Ruth
        - Stone, Walter
        - Stouffer, ? [Lenya's friend in Switzerland]
        - Symonette, Randolphe
      - Photographs, 1961; 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 122)
        - Tuck, Wilhelmina
        - Young, Louise
        - Weigel, Helene
        - West, Mae
      - Lenya's godchildren, n.d.; 51 items. (Box 65, Folder 123)
      - Unidentified individuals, 1949-1974; 56 items. (Box 65, Folder 124-125)
    - Groups of others, VI.N.2
      - Photographs, 1965-1976; 14 items. (Box 65, Folder 126)
        - Brecht and [Ruth Berlauer?]
        - Wilhelm Brückner-Rüggeberg and family
        - Lillian Gish and Ted Mitchell
        - Mary Buckwitz, etc.
        - Russell Detwiler with Anna
        - Krebs and Ted Mitchell
        - S. Neil Fujita and Aiko Fujita and family
        - Joel Grey and Margo Harris
      - Photographs, 1957-1980; 15 items. (Box 65, Folder 127)
        - Halpern, etc.
        - Lita and Lois Hornick
        - Margarethe Kaiser and Russell Detwiler
        - Anna Krebs and others
        - Lichthorn and others
        - Lubke, Heinrich
        - Gigi McGuire and others
        - Gerda Ragalyi and others
        - Richard Siemanowski and
        - Sir John Gielgud and Golda Meir
        - Ruth and Walter Stone
        - Guy Stern and family
        - Igor and Vera Stravinsky
      - Unidentified groups of people, 27 items. (Box 65, Folder 128)
  - Pets, VI.O
    - Kurt Weill/Lenya pets, as well as pets belonging to others, 36 items. (Box 65, Folder 129)
  - New City, VI.P
    - New City and Kurt Weill's grave, 1962-1981; 90 items. (Box 65, Folder 130-131)
  - Photographs of Paintings, VI.Q
    - Paintings by Russell Detwiler and others, 43 items. (Box 65, Folder 132)
  - Miscellaneous, VI.R
    - Scenery and miscellaneous photographs, 108 items. (Box 65, Folder 133)
  - Slides and Negatives, VI.S
    - Miscellaneous negatives and slides arranged chronologically, 1959-1976; ca. 200 items. (Box 66, Folder 134-135)
- Documents, 1913-1981; Series VII; .4' (1 box)
  Documents are divided into two subseries. The first is arranged chronologically. The subseries "B. Passports" is arranged by the person to whom they belong.
  - Contracts, Certificates, and Deeds Belonging to Weill and Lenya, VII.A
    - Declaration of the coming of age of Kurt Weill, written and signed by his father, Albert Weill, and bearing the stamp of Albert Weill, [1913?] (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Sheet of government bonds from the German Reich with a maturity date of 1927 Sep. 1, 1923 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Certificate of nationality for Kurt Weill, 1925 Oct. 1
    - Certificate from the municipal board of Vienna belonging to Lenya, 1925 Oct. 20
    - Contract between Lenya and the Volksbühne Norden to play the role of "Maria" in Was Ihr Wollt, [1920s?]
    - Death certificate of Lenya's father, Franz Blamauer, 1928 Dec. 1
    - Typed letter, signed from Dr. Herzfeld (lawyer) to Kurt Weill, Klein-Machnow, 1933 Nov. 14., 1933 Oct.-Nov.
      Enclosed: Court statement (Potsdam) of expenses for divorce proceedings between Kurt Weill and Lenya.
      Pencil note in Lenya's [?] hand on bottom of first page: "Ich habe das gleiche und bezahle nichts."
      Dated: 1933 Oct. 16.
    - Steuererklärung für 1935..., 1936 May 20
    - Marriage service and certificate of Kurt Weill and Lenya, 1937 Jan. 19
    - The Eternal Road estimated budget of operating costs beginning Feb. 8th, 1937 Feb. 4
    - Agreement for joint bank account between Kurt Weill and Lenya, 1940 Dec. 17 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Indenture between Rollo Peters and Amy Murray and Kurt Weill and Lenya for Brook House and property in New City, New York, 1941 May 13
    - Deed from Rollo Peters/Amy Murray to Kurt Weill and Lenya for house and property in New City, 1941 May 13
    - Closing statement - Peters to Kurt Weill
      1941 May 28.
    - Certificate of Title to premises in New City, 1941 May 28
    - Release of Lease between Kathryn Fallon (owner) and Kurt Weill (tenant), 1941 Jul. 8
    - Affidavit from Aline McMahon to the State of New York, certifying that Kurt Weill had complete control of the Lunchtime Follies project, 1943 Jan.
    - United States. Army. Aircraft Warning Service, [ca. 1943]
      Observer Identification Card.
    - Deed for property from William J. Myers to Kurt Weill and Maxwell Anderson, 1950 Jan. 9 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Deed between Mount Repose Cemetery and Lenya and Maxwell and Gertrude M. Anderson, 1950 Apr. 28
    - Death certificate of Lenya's mother, Johanna Heinisch, 1951 Feb. 7
    - Deed for property from Maxwell Anderson to Lenya, 1952 Jan. 15
    - Apartment lease belonging to Lenya, 1960 Aug. 11 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Landlord's Report to Lease and Application for Increase of Maximum Rent, 1960 Oct.-Nov.
      Enclosed in typed letter.
    - Landlord's Application for Increase of Maximum Rent, 1961 Jun. 22
    - Certification of Lenya to the sole literary and artistic rights of Kurt Weill from the Société des Auteurs et Compositeurs Dramatiques, 1962 Aug. 21
      Copies of Kurt Weill's will laid in.
    - Statement by Lenya with the Vereinsbank in Hamburg giving power of attorney to Anna Krebs., 1971 Jul. 1
    - Screen Actors Guild agreement between Lenya and David Merrick for services in the role of "Mrs. Pelf" in the film Semi-Tough, 1976 Oct. 7
    - Unsigned copy of statement acknowledging receipt of rental materials for Two Movements for String Ouartet, 1977 Apr. 3
    - Legislative Resolution of the State of New York honoring Kurt Weill and Lenya, 1978 Apr. 4
      Program laid in.
    - New York. Workmen's Compensation Board. Notice of Compliance, 1978 May 22
      To Lenya.
    - Police accident report involving Lenya, 1980 Apr. 6
    - Insurance binder for renewal of policy held by Lenya, 1980 Aug. 17
    - New York. Rockland County, 1981 May 9
      Proclamation recognizing the achievements of Lenya and Kurt Weill.
    - Sketches of lands belonging to Lenya
    - Statement acknowledging receipt of rental parts for Happy End.
  - Passports, VII.B
    - Passports (3) belonging to Kurt Weill, 1931-1936 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      Immigration card laid in (1937).
    - Passports (9) belonging to Lenya, 1931-1978 (Box 67, Folder 7-8)
      Includes Certificate of Registration and International Certificate of Vaccination.
    - Passports (3) belonging to George Davis and Russell Detwiler, 1930-1968 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Writings by Weill and Lenya, 1937-1980; Series VIII; .8' (2 boxes)
  Writings by Lenya and Weill are divided into two subseries: A. By Weill; and B. By Lenya. Each of these is then divided into miscellaneous writings, which are arranged alphabetically by title, and diaries, which are arranged chronologically.
  - Writings by Weill, VIII.A
    - Miscellaneous writings, VIII.A.1
      - About the music for "You and me" / Kurt Weill, 1937 May 24.; [4] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - A Coke, a Sandwich and Us / by Kurt Weill, [6] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 2)
        Re the "Lunch Time Follies."
      - [Dream outline], [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 3)
        Typescript with pencil additions in Kurt Weill's hand.
        Title from discarded folder.
      - [Huckleberry Finn], 1950 Jan.; [4] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 4)
        On first sheet: "My outline. January 1950."
      - I married a king: a story idea for a motion picture / by Kurt Weill, n.d.; 3 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 5)
        Typescript with pencil and ink corrections by Kurt Weill.
      - Jeptha's Tochter, n.d.; [2] p.; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Kurt Weill, n.d.; 4 sheets; 36 cm. (Box 68, Folder 7)
        Notes by Kurt Weill re his American career on Playwright's Company stationery.
      - Kurt Weill's notes on Street Scene, n.y. Dec. 21.; [4] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 8)
        On Schubert Theatre stationery with the names "Mr. Wiman, Mr. Rice, Mr. Hughes, Mr. Friedman" on the first page.
      - Man of the Hour, n.d.; 3 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - [Nell Quinn notes], 1937-1942?; [9] p.; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Notes about the musical settings of Helen Hayes' recordings, n.d.; [2] p.; 27 cm. (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Notes for "Knickerbocker Holiday" picture, 1939 Dec. 5.; [2] sheets; 27 cm. (Box 68, Folder 11)
        At end in pencil in Kurt Weill's hand: Suffern, N.Y.
      - Notes on Broadway and the musical theatre / Kurt Weill, [3] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Notes to the score of "One Touch of Venus", n.d.; [2] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Oper in Amerika / Kurt Weill, n.d.; [9] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Plan for a series of radio operas / by Kurt Weill (composer), 1937 Jul. 14.; [2], 4, 3 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Prospectus of comedy sketches in Lunchtime Follies radio show, n.d.; [2] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Report of the Dramatists' Guild Committee for Investigation of the Broadway Producing situation by Kurt Weill (chairman), n.d.; 4 sheets; 26 cm. (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Scenario for "The Pirate", n.d.; [17] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 15)
        Three pages of pencil notes in Kurt Weill's hand (27 cm.) laid in.
      - Two Dreams-Come-True / by Kurt Weill, [ca. 1947?].; [3] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 16)
        Program notes for the 1947 Columbia Masterworks Recording of Street Scene?.
      - [What is musical theatre?], n.d.; [2] p.; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 17)
        "Lecture for Group Theatre" - note on discarded folder.
      - Miscellaneous notes and ideas [Reply to Harold Clurman], [3] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 18)
        Holograph in pencil and typescript.
        Typed transcription of the pencil notes on Kurt Weill Foundation stationery (and copy) laid in.
        Title from heading on the typed transcription.
      - [Thoughts on the Broadway Theatre], n.d.; [8] p.; 11 x 16 cm. (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - [Eternal Road], n.d.; [7] p.; 17 cm. (Box 68, Folder 18)
        Title from discarded envelope.
      - [American minstrel show history], n.d.; [24] p.; 8 x 13 cm. (Box 68, Folder 18)